Lucky! The concert's almost over, change into a t-shirt and reset
ラッキ — ！ LIVE終わり大体  Tシャツ着替えて  リセット
Like it! It’s a brand-new you, say bye-bye to
Like it！  新しい自分  あの日のブル — なんて
the blues you felt on that day! Let’s go!
Bye-bye！ Let's go！
Check out this piece! Check out this piece!
ピ — ス de check！  ピ — ス de check！
Check out this piece! Che-che-check it out!
ピ — ス de Check！  Che-che-check it out！
Check out this piece! Piece-ful days!
ピ — ス de check！  ピ — スFUL DAYS！
Get it, get it, get it, it's on the verge of selling out!
Get it get it get it  売り切れ寸前！
We've pledged with a badge pin with the school emblem shining bright on our chest
校章ピンバッチ胸にキラリ誓ったんだ
Wave the flag with the diagram
ダイアグラムでフラッグ振れ
Punch up at the air with a pumpkin glove beam until your arm hurts
パンプキングロ — ブビ — ム痛いほど punching
In our stickers we've placed a heartfelt message for you
ステッカ — には熱いメッセ — ジ for you
One, two, three, four, five, so-so-so-SOLD OUT!
One, two, three, four, five, so-so-so  ソ — ルドアウト！
Hey guys, items always end up selling out during the pre-sales, sorry
Hey guys, 先行販売でアイテム売り切れいつもゴメン
What, again?!
え — , またか！？
There's only a few photo sets left
Photo set, 残りわずかです
Ugh, they should at least be able to print out more photos right on the spot, shouldn't they!?
写真ぐらいすぐそこで焼いてこれるだろ！
Sorry!
ごめんなさい！
Check out this piece! Check out this piece!
ピ — ス de check！  ピ — ス de check！
Check out this piece! Che-che-check it out!
ピ — ス de Check！  Che-che-check it out！
Check out this piece! Piece-ful DAYS!
ピ — ス de check！  ピ — スFUL DAYS！
Get it, get it, get it, it's on the verge of selling out!
Get it get it get it  売り切れ寸前！
We've pledged with a badge pin with the school emblem shining bright on our chest
校章ピンバッチ胸にキラリ誓ったんだ
Wave the flag with the diagram
ダイアグラムでフラッグ振れ
Punch up at the air with a pumpkin glove beam until your arm hurts
パンプキングロ — ブビ — ム痛いほど punching
In our stickers we've placed a heartfelt message for you
ステッカ — には熱いメッセ — ジ for you
One, two, three, four, five, here we go, here we go!
One, two, three, four, five, いくよ Here we go！
My collection of items increased, gimme, check it out!
アイテム増えたの gimme チェキラ！
Please, please, please, please, let me get the random-bonus in really random manner!
Please Please Please Please  ランダム封入！
Find me, look for the one with me on it!
Find me  私を見つけてよ
The one I always get is So-nano, So-nano, Soyo…
当たるのいつも Soナノ､ Soナノ､ 爽葉なの…
What!? You don't like Soyo!? Well, fine then, give it back!!!
えっ！？  爽葉じゃ嫌なの！？  じゃあ、返して — ！！！
What? Well, I'll take it then~!!
えっ,  じゃあ,  私もらっちゃいま〜す！！
Check out this piece! Check out this piece!
ピ — ス de check！  ピ — ス de check！
Check out this piece! Che-che-check it out!
ピ — ス de Check！  Che-che-check it out！
Check out this piece! Piece-ful DAYS!
ピ — ス de check！  ピ — スFUL DAYS！
Get it, get it, get it, it's on the verge of selling out!
Get it get it get it  売り切れ寸前！
Never forget Article 7 of the creed inside our student handbook
生徒手帳ん中忘れるな信条７か条
Staining our towels, our sweat and tears flash
タオル滲んだ  汗涙フラッシュ
Seize it, rolling rolling stones!
掴め rolling rolling stones
This line up is fiery hot with strong emotion
強い気持ちで温めたよこのラインナップ
Don't pass it up, get your hands on it, okay? Do your best!
見逃さずに手にいれてね Fighting！
Please try and check it out by all means, catch it!
是非チェックしてみてください Catching！